<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/blog</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/blog"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2014-04-03T20:00:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Wunderground with the LaCrosse C84612</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/blog/2014/04/04/wunderground-with-the-lacrosse-c84612.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/blog/2014/04/04/wunderground-with-the-lacrosse-c84612.html</id>
    <published>2014-04-03T20:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2016-03-17T20:13:37-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I got a &lt;a href="http://www.lacrossetechnology.com/c84612/"&gt;La Crosse C84612&lt;/a&gt; weather station as a gift.  Costco sold this model sometime last year, though now the closest thing they have is a quite expensive &lt;a href="http://www.costco.com/Oregon-Scientific-WMR300-Ultra-Precision-Professional-Weather-System.product.100086588.html"&gt;Oregon Scientific unit&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The La Crosse has been a great weather station for me: easy to set up, accurate reporting, and no interaction required.  One of the features it came with that I was most excited about was internet connetivity.  The station comes with a gateway that wirelessly (900MHz, not wifi) links up with the other components of the weather station, which also link wirelessly.  Good system in theory, but it's only set up to send data to La Crosse Alerts™, a website which I can best describe as functional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/dinomite/13623412293/"&gt;&lt;img src="https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7241/13623412293_bdc93cd82f_z.jpg" alt="The main view of La Crosse Alerts™" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the output of the gateway is simply data on the wire, I figured it'd be possible to capture the communication between the gateway and the La Crosse Alerts™ server.  The first step in such a journey is to look around and see what other folks have found, and what a productive step that was this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stumbled across a &lt;a href="http://www.wxforum.net/index.php?topic=14299.0"&gt;thread on WXForum&lt;/a&gt; of folks discussing the GW1000U, which is the gateway that is part of the C84612 weather station.  If you read through there, you'll see that &lt;a href="http://www.wxforum.net/index.php?action=profile;u=11566"&gt;skydvrz&lt;/a&gt; has put in a ton of effort and reverse engineer the communication.  He has written a Windows program that takes the place of the La Crosse Alerts server, collecting data from the gateway and storing it in MySQL.  Create an account on the forum and ask skydvrz for the latest code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best part about this replacement server is that it sends dtaa to Weather Underground, which has a &lt;a href="http://www.wunderground.com/weatherstation/WXDailyHistory.asp?ID=KVAARLIN28"&gt;much better interface for weather stations&lt;/a&gt;, providing history &amp;amp; graphs that are far superior to La Crosse's site.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Making 1080p Timelapses with Lightroom</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/blog/2014/02/13/making-1080p-timelapses-with-lightroom.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/blog/2014/02/13/making-1080p-timelapses-with-lightroom.html</id>
    <published>2014-02-12T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-03-14T10:41:27-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;There are &lt;a href="http://photographyforrealestate.net/2012/09/09/how-to-use-lightroom-4-to-create-a-time-lapse-video/"&gt;a bunch&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href="http://lightroom-blog.com/2013/09/17/timelapse-again-in-lightroom-5-2/"&gt;tutorials&lt;/a&gt; for creating time-lapse videos in Lightroom.  All of the ones I found only provide a preset for making 1280x720 (720p) videos.  I took one of those presets and updated it to be make a &lt;a href="/assets/JPEG 82 (1080p).lrtemplate"&gt;1920x1080 (1080p) video from stills&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Download this an add it to your Lightroom video presets.  On Mac, this is located at &lt;code&gt;~/Library/Application Support/Adobe/Lightroom/Export Presets/Video/&lt;/code&gt;.  For Windows, &lt;a href="http://store.apple.com/us"&gt;see here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="footnotes"&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id="fn:1"&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Seriously not trying to be a dick, I just don't fucking know and give zero shits &lt;a href="#fnref:1" class="reversefootnote"&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>at(1) on Mac OS X</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/blog/2014/02/03/at-1-on-mac-os-x.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/blog/2014/02/03/at-1-on-mac-os-x.html</id>
    <published>2014-02-02T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-03-14T10:41:27-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;at(1) is a standard command in &lt;a href="http://www.freebsd.org/cgi/man.cgi?query=at&amp;amp;sektion=1"&gt;every&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://unixhelp.ed.ac.uk/CGI/man-cgi?at"&gt;Unix-like&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.openbsd.org/cgi-bin/man.cgi?query=at&amp;amp;apropos=0&amp;amp;sektion=0&amp;amp;manpath=OpenBSD+Current&amp;amp;arch=i386&amp;amp;format=html"&gt;operating&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.shrubbery.net/solaris9ab/SUNWaman/hman1/at.1.html"&gt;system&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://illumos.org/man/1/at"&gt;that&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.unix.com/man-page/opensolaris/1/at/"&gt;I&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://plan9.bell-labs.com/magic/man2html?man=at&amp;amp;sect=1"&gt;know&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://netbsd.gw.com/cgi-bin/man-cgi?at++NetBSD-current"&gt;of&lt;/a&gt;, including &lt;a href="https://developer.apple.com/library/mac/documentation/Darwin/Reference/ManPages/man1/at.1.html"&gt;Mac OS&lt;/a&gt;, for scheduling tasks to be run at a later time.  Unfortunately, OS X doesn't run (or even seem to have) atd(8), the daemon responsible for running at(1)-scheduled tasks.  Complicating matters is the fact that at(1) is a very difficult to search for, because search engines strip such common words, so figuring out such issues can't really be done with even the best searching.  So here I'll list other things that one might search for: atq, atrm, and batch, which are all part of the at(1) suite of tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My (likely vain) hope is that this post will spread a bit of knowledge and maybe catch searches, if someone's searches match my description.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Anti-pull dog harnesses</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/blog/2014/01/25/anti-pull-dog-harnesses.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/blog/2014/01/25/anti-pull-dog-harnesses.html</id>
    <published>2014-01-24T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-03-17T19:57:00-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zH64dlgyydM"&gt;I like dogs&lt;/a&gt; and recently got a beaglish one of my own from the &lt;a href="http://www.lostdogrescue.org/"&gt;Lost Dog Foundation&lt;/a&gt;.  While wonderful, he has the affliction of walking excitement common to hunting hounds—appropriate to his name, Scout wants to lead the way and suss out any squirrels to be found.  At only 25 pounds, he won't drag you down the street, but the constant tugging on the leash is tiring.  I've tried a number of collars &amp;amp; harnesses to try to combat this problem, and what follows are my opinions on them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/dinomite/11892424355/"&gt;&lt;img src="http://farm6.staticflickr.com/5471/11892424355_bd7c2bcc67_z.jpg" alt="Scout being Rowdy" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="illusion-collarhttpwwwcesarswaycomshopillusion-dog-collar-leash-system"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cesarsway.com/shop/Illusion-Dog-Collar-Leash-System"&gt;Illusion Collar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My girlfriend had been watching a lot of &lt;a href="http://www.cesarsway.com/"&gt;Caesar Millan&lt;/a&gt; before we got our dog and we put a fair bit of stock in his methods.  Using a leash in the way that &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vjub9dCBiv8"&gt;Caesar describes&lt;/a&gt;, well up the dog's neck and close to the ears, allowed us to control Scout, but the leash wouldn't stay there, so we figured it was worth trying the oddly-named&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Illusion Collar to make this easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the Illusion collar does what it's supposed to, keeping the operative part of the collar well up the dog's neck for better control, this did nothing for Scout and he remaiined unruly on walks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="petsafe-easy-walk-harnesshttpwwwamazoncomgpproductb0009zbkg4refaslisstlieutf8camp1789creative390957creativeasinb0009zbkg4linkcodeas2tagdinomitenet-20"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0009ZBKG4/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B0009ZBKG4&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=dinomitenet-20"&gt;PetSafe Easy Walk Harness&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've found this harness to be by far the most effective.  The harness has a circle of straps around the dog's body, just behind their shoulders and a strap across the dog's chest.  The front strap has a cinching portion to which the leash clips, tightening a bit when the dog pulls.  More importantly, because the attachment is on the dog's chest, the force of any pulling turns them sideways, greatly limiting thier ability to pull.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The downside to the Easy Walk is that the strap behind the dog's front legs can rub their fur-less armpits raw, as I've found with Scout and other friends have reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="freedom-no-pull-harnesshttpwwwamazoncomgpproductb0085xohdurefaslisstlieutf8camp1789creative390957creativeasinb0085xohdulinkcodeas2tagdinomitenet-20"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0085XOHDU/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B0085XOHDU&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=dinomitenet-20"&gt;Freedom No-Pull Harness&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is set up similarly to the PetSafe Easy Walk mentioned above, but with additional versatility.  Like the PetSafe it has an attachment point on the dog's chest, with all of the noted advantages &amp;amp; disadvantages, though the front attachment on the Freedom No-Pull isn't cinching.  Where it does have a cinching attachment point is on the dog's back between their shoulder blades.  Using this attachment doesn't provide nearly the pulling prevention of the front attachment, but it does keep from driving the underbody strap into the dog's armpits and chafing them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The intended arrangement is to clip a leash into both attachments and use it like a horse's reins—tug on the front one when the dog pulls to correct the behavior.  This is effective, but it does halve the length of your leash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="footnotes"&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id="fn:1"&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The Illusion collar is named after his estranged wife Ilusión &lt;a href="#fnref:1" class="reversefootnote"&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>GORUCK Challenge</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/blog/2013/06/27/goruck-challenge-preparation.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/blog/2013/06/27/goruck-challenge-preparation.html</id>
    <published>2013-06-26T20:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2016-03-17T20:17:39-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/dinomite/9157378869/"&gt;&lt;img src="https://farm4.staticflickr.com/3713/9157378869_d05b4078ef_z.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
Photo credit: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/troyangrignon"&gt;Troy Angrignon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did the &lt;a href="https://www.goruck.com/events/Challenge"&gt;GORUCK Challenge&lt;/a&gt; last
weekend.  The GORUCK Challenge is a 12 hour guided tour of a city, led by
special forces guys known as the Cadre.  Every challenge, even in the same city,
is a different experience, tailored by the Cadre based upon their desires, the
folks on the team, and what the city has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="class-662-summary"&gt;Class 662 Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A team of 34 people, each with a 45-55 pound rucksack hiked &amp;amp; ran 20 miles
around San Francisco over the course of 12 hours.  We were accompanied by two 30
pound bags of quarters, a ~100 pound log, and, for about half of the time,
a ~300 pound couch adorned with a 210-230 pound person. In the last few hours,
we swapped the couch for a pair of 250 pound logs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="difficulty"&gt;Difficulty&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall the event was a &lt;em&gt;ton&lt;/em&gt; of fun.  Having read numerous things in the weeks
leading up to this, my first challenge, I had gotten a bit worried.  The number
of people who listed this as the hardest thing they'd ever done and hinted
at the misery they endured made it sound like a rough, "Well, I'm glad I did
that. Once." sort of thing.  Nothing could be further from the truth.  If
you're physically capable, you'll have a good time until the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do I mean by capable?  I don't think a single test other than the Challenge
itself (or perhaps doing a Light and saying it was easy) could make it clear,
but I can put it in CrossFit terms.  CrossFit + weight lifting is my main
regimen, 3-4 days a week at &lt;a href="http://www.patriotcrossfit.com/blog/"&gt;Patriot CrossFit&lt;/a&gt;
in Arlington if you want to get an idea of the programming.  I'm certainly no
firebreather, but I manage to do a majority of the workouts as prescribed and
in fairly good time.  If you can follow the &lt;a href="http://www.crossfit.com/"&gt;main site&lt;/a&gt;,
doing half of the workouts as prescribed without being horribly slow, you'll be
fine.  You need not be &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xJ27XzR3HJc"&gt;Jason Kaplan&lt;/a&gt;
to be in good enough shape—my 7 minute Fran is enough to make the Challenge a
non-killer event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id="notes-on-preparation"&gt;Notes on Preparation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id="hydration"&gt;Hydration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I say hydration here because I think something more than water is important.
I used a &lt;a href="https://www.goruck.com/Gear/Details/low-profile-hydration-bladder"&gt;low-profile SOURCE bladder&lt;/a&gt;
which fit well in the main compartment between my bricks and the main flap.
I filled it with water and 6 &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001QW1L72/ref=as_li_ss_til?tag=dinomitenet-20&amp;amp;camp=0&amp;amp;creative=0&amp;amp;linkCode=as4&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B001QW1L72&amp;amp;adid=16NHVNWNJT4379CHRA7K&amp;amp;"&gt;Nuun tablets&lt;/a&gt;
initially, and tossed in a few more tablets when I refilled at around 0300.  We
didn't stop for water again and I was out near the end of the challenge, along
with most of the team.  If my next Challenge is anywhere warmer, I'll find a way
to have a second bladder or even a couple of Nalgenes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="food"&gt;Food&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I often deride cyclists for their obsession with fast carbs, thinking that
without sucking down maltodextrin every 20 minutes they might just go from being
a world-class überathelete on their Yellow Polkadot Single Baller Edition
Cervélo to a prole riding a Mongoose.  But it is to cyclists whom I turned when
gathering supplies for this challenge.  In the end, I downed seven gels and two
packs of chewie jobbies throughout the 12 hours.  Are those absolutely
necessary?  Not at all, I could have gotten through without any of that and
gone strict paleo with some bananas or some such.  But it would have sucked.
Having good blood sugar support after glycogen stores are depleted increases
your ability to perform for sure; more importantly, the carbohydrate combined
with caffeine improves mood, keeping the event from being a gruelling death
march.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So hit up your local bike shop and get some of those goofy fast acting
carbohydrate sources.  I had a couple of &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0010TADUW/ref=as_li_ss_til?tag=dinomitenet-20&amp;amp;camp=0&amp;amp;creative=0&amp;amp;linkCode=as4&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B0010TADUW&amp;amp;adid=01XQGWDWXR3T3TSYGRMM&amp;amp;"&gt;Honey Stingers&lt;/a&gt;
(which are mostly honey) but most of what I brought were caffeinated (35mg or
70mg depending on the flavor) &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B007I6NLFU/ref=as_li_ss_til?tag=dinomitenet-20&amp;amp;camp=0&amp;amp;creative=0&amp;amp;linkCode=as4&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B007I6NLFU&amp;amp;adid=0YDREPJX49416514ZN73&amp;amp;"&gt;Gu Roctane&lt;/a&gt;
energy gels.  I drink tea regularly, so I think the regular-strength (35mg) ones
were best for me.  Next time I'll probably bring 10 gels along with a bunch of
the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0041HKO3G/ref=as_li_ss_til?tag=dinomitenet-20&amp;amp;camp=0&amp;amp;creative=0&amp;amp;linkCode=as4&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B0041HKO3G&amp;amp;adid=1KMX5P2VRMECJ8Q9Q0NJ&amp;amp;"&gt;chewie versions&lt;/a&gt;.
The chewies are amazingly delightful after you've speed marched across the city.
If you're the prepared sort, it'd be good to bring some extra.  Even amongst
such a rarefied group there are knuckleheads who bring little to no food.  If
someone's performance falls off, a caffeinated gel is a great way to bring them
back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also brought a few bars (Luna or UberFood, I think) but only ate one.  It's
nice to have something different during a long break (5 minutes).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="clothing"&gt;Clothing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This challenge was during June in San Francisco.  For those who don't know,
that's winter.  Paradoxically, it wasn't windy &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; foggy that night, but it was
a bit cold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wore Under Armour leggings, some Champion workout shorts, &lt;a href="http://www.drymaxsocks.com/running_hyper_thin.php"&gt;Drymax socks&lt;/a&gt;,
a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00275Q8ZW/ref=as_li_ss_til?tag=dinomitenet-20&amp;amp;camp=0&amp;amp;creative=0&amp;amp;linkCode=as4&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B00275Q8ZW&amp;amp;adid=0JWP8VED4W44F2TK8VZ7&amp;amp;"&gt;padded football shirt&lt;/a&gt;,
a long-sleeve Under Armour Cold Gear top, and a workout shirt over that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unsure of my shoe choice up until the day of The Challenge, I settled on Inov8
F-Lite 195s.  I've been wearing minimalist shoes (Merrel Trail Gloves are my
favorites) exclusively for a few years now, but I was concerned that the extra
weight on my back would lead to a Bad Time for my feet &amp;amp; knees.  I had bought
some F-Lite 230s which were what I had planed on until the day of, but I settled
on the 195s because my feet feel better in them.  They were just fine, despite
the weight and surfaces we were walking on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.fieggen.com/shoelace/surgeonknot.htm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.fieggen.com/Dont_Link/FinishedSurgeonKnot1.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other thing you need to do is &lt;a href="http://www.fieggen.com/shoelace/surgeonknot.htm"&gt;tie your shoes properly&lt;/a&gt;.
If you can slip your shoes off without untying them, they aren't tied properly.
We had to stop multiple times during our first time hack in which we needed to
cover 3.5 miles in 35 minutes due to shoes that came untied or got flat tired.
Properly tying your shoes completely prevents both of these and will keep your
teammates from thinking you're incompetent from the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pockets.  You want pockets.  Movements are often an hour or more, during which
time you don't have opportunity to dig around your pack for the aforementioned
sugary delights.  Every time you stop, ensure your pockets have a gel or two in
them.  Pockets are also where you'll shove the trash after you down one of those
as cadre are strict about littering, rightly so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="your-ruck"&gt;Your Ruck&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/dinomite/9159389132/"&gt;&lt;img src="https://farm6.staticflickr.com/5540/9159389132_4c88fea201_c.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/dinomite/9159343672/"&gt;&lt;img class="image-right" src="https://farm4.staticflickr.com/3667/9159343672_fa6d911781.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do something to your ruck so that you can differentiate it from everyone elses.
All cadre are different, but you'll end up taking your ruck off and passing it
to teammates at some point in the night, and if they all look the same, it's
impossible to find your own.  I had a light-colored War Stories &amp;amp; Free Beer
patch so that I could identify my GR1 from the back; the loops of cord that I
use to hold my hydration tube makes it notable from the front.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having a black Omega carabiner clipped through three MOLLE sure does look cool,
but it's not particularly funcitonal.  I have one on my ruck and it's nice for
briefly attaching a water bottle or my bike helmet, but it's really difficult
to remove for other uses.  When your ruck is jammed full of bricks, water, and
yoga blocks, you can't manipulate the fabric enough to remove the 'biner
easily, so save yourself the hassle and have it only clipped through two loops
so that it's faster to get at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="other-junk"&gt;Other Junk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimize it, but don't go crazy.  There are endless words written to the effect
of "if you're not sure, don't bring it".  I largely subscribe to this mentality,
as you most likely aren't going to need things, but there's a dose of realism
that is needed here.  Between the 30 pounds of bricks and the 10 pounds of
water and misc that are the minimum weight, you aren't going to notice a few
extra food bars, gels, or a windbreaker, so don't sweat it.  If the weather is
on the edge of being cold, bring the windbreaker.  I always carry a Sharpie &amp;amp;
a pen in my ruck day to day and was sad that I didn't have them when we needed
to write things down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things to certainly not bring are those that will absorb water.  Carrying around
a small portion of your local body of water is a bad time.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Packing Bricks for the GORUCK Challenge</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/blog/2012/12/03/packing-bricks-for-the-goruck-challenge.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/blog/2012/12/03/packing-bricks-for-the-goruck-challenge.html</id>
    <published>2012-12-02T19:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-03-17T20:12:56-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/dinomite/8248913885/in/photostream/"&gt;&lt;img class="image-right" src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8486/8248913885_8828ee2a54.jpg" alt="GORUCK GR Echo with 4 bricks &amp;amp; yoga block" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have finally signed up for a &lt;a href="https://www.goruckchallenge.com/"&gt;GORUCK Challenge&lt;/a&gt;.  The event is 6 months off, but thanks to Jason posting &lt;a href="http://www.gorucknews.com/challenge/wrapping-bricks-explained/"&gt;Wrapping Bricks Explained&lt;/a&gt; I've been playing around with packing bricks in my rucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I followed the instructions on the above mentioned post for wrapping the bricks in pairs and took Asha Wagner's &lt;a href="http://nuffsaid6.blogspot.com/2011/11/goruck-tough-sf-class-086.html"&gt;advice for securing the bricks&lt;/a&gt; in a GORUCK pack using &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B007A2XFYE/ref=as_li_ss_til?tag=dinomitenet-20&amp;amp;camp=0&amp;amp;creative=0&amp;amp;linkCode=as4&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B007A2XFYE&amp;amp;adid=14454BYTXX0X67M3EC7K&amp;amp;"&gt;Sea to Summit 3/4" straps&lt;/a&gt; to secure them on the ruck's internal &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pouch_Attachment_Ladder_System"&gt;PALS webbing&lt;/a&gt;.  To the right are two pairs of bricks (4 total) in a GR Echo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm pretty light, just under 150 most days, so 4 bricks is the prescription.  A yoga block is the perfect thing to fill the extra space—dense but soft and about the size of two bricks.  One note is that you can indeed fit 6 bricks into a GR Echo, with just a bit of room to spare.  The third package of bricks takes the place of the yoga block, with a bit of space on either side.  Unfortunately, there isn't nearly enough space for a hydration bladder along with them.  If you're taking 6 bricks to the Challenge, get a GR1 or Radio Ruck.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
